Do you happen to know anything about my father's accident?
What kind of accident it was and how it happened...
Well, all I know is that it was a car accident.
At night, a speeding car tried to pass your father's car and...
What?
Chief Seo.
Team Leader Ko.
You didn't go to work?
Yes, I'm heading in soon. Are you here to see Grandfather?
Yes. I saw him, and now I'm on my way to work.
Okay, please go ahead.
I have something to ask Secretary Ju.
I see. I'm on my way to work anyway.
I can wait, and we can go together.
It's all right. You go ahead. This might take a while.
All right, then.
- Take care, Chief Seo. - Yes.
Then do you know anything about the driver...
who caused the accident?
I think I heard he turned himself. and for involuntary manslaughter,
he was sentenced to five years.
Hey, why are you still here?
Yes. I'm leaving.
I don't know anything else.
But Gyeol, did you really lose all your memories from back then?
Yes.
Then why are you suddenly curious?
It's not like it's a good memory.
Thank you. I should get going.
What? You came all this way, and you're leaving...
- without seeing the Chairman? - I have to get straight to work.
I'll see Grandfather next time I visit.
Hey, but...
Why is he suddenly asking about that accident?
Gyeol was here?
Yes.
He asked me about his father's accident 25 years ago.
He asked if I knew anything about it.
What? Why all of a sudden?
It seems Gyeol has lost all his memories of that time.
I wonder if he suddenly remembered something.
I have to go prune some branches, so I'll be on my way.
- All right. Thank you. - Yes.
What's wrong?
Is something worrying you?
No, it's nothing to worry about.
Do you remember when Gyeol was a child?
The day he came to this house and started talking again.
Of course. How could I ever forget that day?
Dad.
Gyeol.
Dad. Dad!
Dad.
I think Gyeol is finally ready to face the pain he has kept...
- buried deep inside for so long. - Oh, dear.
I just hope he doesn't get hurt.
Father, Mother. Is there anything you need?
No. Why do you ask?
Well, if you think about it, I'm sure there must be something.
I just really want to do something for you.
I was thinking of calling Yeon Soon. We can all have lunch together.
What? You're seeing Ms. Kang Yeon Ja again?
Yes. You should call her.
You've missed 50 years of being with her.
So you should see each other as much as possible. Of course.
From now on,
you will treat each other with the proper respect.
- She's your sister-in-law. - What? My sister-in-law?
If she's my sister-in-law...
Oh, then she's like my "Sis."
Who calls their sister-in-law "Sis" these days?
Just act the way you always have.
No, I can't. She's my esteemed sister-in-law.
Thank you, General Director.
- Why are you suddenly thanking me? - What?
Well, I took a long vacation for personal reasons,
and you were so understanding....
Han Ji Hun, please upload the latest version...
of our team's Joy upgrade.
What? Oh, yes.
The third competition will include aspects...
of the first and second competitions,
and most importantly, the site selection.
Since this is a comprehensive evaluation,
I hope you all will approach it with the mindset of...
a completely fresh start.
- Yes, understood. - Yes, understood.
By the way, where is everyone from Team Two?
Oh, Team Leader Ko is on his way back...
from some off-site business. Mr. Kim is in the records room.
Off-site business?
- Everyone, keep up the good work. - Yes.
Our team has a meeting, so we will head out first.
Okay, good work.
Can we talk for a minute?
The meeting is in ten minutes, so get to the point.
I'm truly sorry. For trying to copy your file.
And for showing that video during the competition.
All of it.
And thank you for covering for me.
I have not forgiven you, Han Ji Hun.
What do you mean?
I let it slide because I wanted to face off one last time...
against that passionate and capable senior I used to know...
when we first founded Lucky Joy and were developing Joy.
Are you giving me a chance?
Yes. This is the last chance I am giving you, so make it count.
Okay.
I understand what you mean.
Thank you. I will fight with all I have got.
As for Team Leader Ko, make sure you separately...
apologise to him sincerely.
Using someone's weakness was a truly cowardly thing to do.
Yes, I am ashamed of myself.
I will be sure to apologise.
Where did you go without eating breakfast?
To my family's home. I went to see Secretary Ju.
Secretary Ju? Why so suddenly...
I suddenly remembered that Grandfather and Secretary Ju...
came to my father's funeral to pay their respects.
So I asked if he happened to know anything...
- about my father's accident. - Did you find anything out?
No. Grandfather and Secretary Ju rushed there...
after hearing the news of the accident.
From now on, let's find things out slowly.
Let us not be too hasty.
You are right. We should not rush. I was a bit impatient today.
Oh, please keep your schedule free after work today.
Why? Is something the matter?
Yes. Asking you on a first date.
What? A date? But we are together every day.
I am sorry I am late.
I was gathering some materials related to...
selecting overseas sites for the Retirement Community.
- Oh, I see. - Yes.
Site selection is the most important part of the third competition,
so this is very useful data. Good work.
Now, only the final competition is left.
Let's do our best.
Is that lunchbox for me?
Why would this be for you?
It's for your maternal grandmother...
Are you wearing makeup?
And why is your skirt so short?
Why? You said I looked pretty.
You told me to always dress like this.
Go upstairs, change into the sweats you usually wear,
- and come back down. - No. Why?
Come to think of it, I knew you had changed for a while now.
Do you like him? That pretty boy?
What are you talking about? As if I like someone.
Oh, look at you stuttering. It must be true.
What are you talking about? I am swamped with my webtoon.
Anyway, when are you free?
Mom, when am I ever free?
Every day it is the series and everything else.
But why do you ask?
Your maternal grandmother wants to see you kids.
She has seen Eun Ae, but she has never properly met...
you, Eun Hyung, and Bit Na.
Well, I'd like to meet her too.
Oh, aren't they having a living funeral soon?
- We can see her then. - That's a separate occasion.
She said she wants to spend some quality time...
with her grandchildren before that.
So try to make some time soon.
Okay, then. I'll have to coordinate with Eun Hyung to go and see her.
I'll talk to him tonight, and we'll set a date.
- Okay, then. - Have a good time with Grandma.
Make up for lost time and be a good daughter.
Oh, please. You just worry about yourself.
You know what'll happen if you break your curfew, right?
That's so lame. A curfew? Seriously?
I'm heading out.
Yes, it's me.
I'll stop by for a bit later.
Oh, I just thought I'd make you some lunch.
No, that's not it.
Oh, wait.
Five. Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Oh, you're here?
Hye Ji.
No, I mean, Hye Ji what are you doing here?
Why? Are you disappointed to see me?
No, no, it's not that.
I haven't heard from you in a while,
so you showing up all of a sudden just surprised me.
I've been so busy with my final exams.
I'm sorry for not keeping in touch.
Oh, no, it's fine. Really.
Not at all. You have nothing to be sorry about.
Happy Kiss Day to us.
Excuse me? Kiss Day?
Yes, it's Kiss Day, the 44th day since we met,
and it's when you're supposed to have your first kiss.
Gosh.
Oh, Eun Nim, perfect timing.
It's our Kiss Day today. Can you take a picture for us?
What? Kiss Day?
Sure, why not.
Hey, no, no, no.
I mean, what is all this about a Kiss Day?
What are you talking about?
Hurry up and take the picture.
But...
Oh, come on, wait a second.
Hye Ji, this isn't happening. Okay?
Okay, look.
Yes, I might have said "okay" or "deal..."
when I was drunk,
and I am very, very sorry about that.
But did we ever agree to date? Have we even talked on the phone?
This is purely your misunderstanding, Hye Ji.
Is it because of Eun Nim?
- What? - Hey, Hye Ji.
Writer Seo, do you perhaps...
Yes, that is correct.
I have feelings for Writer Jo Eun Nim.
Bung Woo.
Yes, Bung Nim.
Now that it has come to this, I will make my intentions clear.
I like you.
Bung Nim.
What?
Bung Woo, Bung Nim?
Jo Eun Nim, tell me.
Do you like Writer Seo too? Is that it?
Well, I'm not really sure,
but then again, I think I might.
So,
have I been fanning the flames of your little romance?
- Adding fuel to the fire? - Hye Ji, don't misunderstand.
I'm not even sure about my own feelings yet.
Whatever. Good luck, you two. You actually look good together.
What?
Honestly, I was too busy studying to date.
So this is for the best.
I'm just going to focus on the national exam now,
so you two have a lovely romance.
Well then.
Hye Ji.
So...
I already told you that I like you, Bung Nim.
What about you, Bung Nim?
Do you not like me?
No, I don't dislike you.
Does that mean you like me?
No, it's not that I like you.
I just said I don't dislike you.
That's the same thing.
Bung Woo, Bung Nim, you're my witnesses, okay?
No, wait. You're not witnesses. You're the proof.
That's not it.
I'm telling you I'm not sure yet.
Go back to work.
Okay.
You're making cold noodles? That's so much work.
It's no trouble.
I made the broth yesterday and put it in the fridge to chill,
and I also prepared all the toppings.
I just need to boil the noodles.
I was planning on making lunch.
Oh my, you're here, Sister-in-law?
Sister-in-law?
Did you just call me sister-in-law?
Yes, you're my husband's sister, so that makes you my sister-in-law.
And I'm your brother's wife.
So, from now on, instead of calling me...
Min Ho's Mom or Madam,
just call me "sister," sister-in-law.
It's not like I'm your young unmarried sister-in-law.
What's with the "sister-in-law" business?
Just call me what you always have. Honestly...
No, in a prestigious family like ours,
even our titles must be proper and elegant.
When in Rome, you follow Roman law. What are you talking about?
Just call each other whatever you're comfortable with.
I'm sure the titles will sort themselves out over time.
So, what's all this?
Yes, I brought these to make cold noodles for lunch.
My goodness, Kang Yeon Ja.
I mean, you know how to make cold noodles?
I guess the apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
Mother, I heard you used to work...
in a construction site cafeteria kitchen?
And it seems the daughter inherited that talent...
As soon as the Chairman is up,
- I'll start boiling the noodles. - Yes, please do.
By the way, when can I see all my grandchildren?
Did you find out when they're available?
Yes, I asked my youngest daughter today.
She said she'll coordinate with her brother to find a time.
- The one who quit med school? - Yes.
Oh, I want to see my great-granddaughter soon too.
Do you think your son and his wife will get back together?
It seems you have a lot to talk about,
so I'll go back inside.
- Come out when noodles are done. - Yes, sister-in-law.
Oh, have you set a date?
For the Chairman's living funeral.
I'll help you prepare, so please don't overdo it.
Okay, let's do that.
Gosh, this feels like a dream.
I can't believe I am standing face to face to you like this.
It's like a reunion of separated families, isn't it?
What? Bring everyone home, including the great-granddaughter?
Are you busy?
Why? Did something happen again?
There's always something. Kang Yeon Ja is here...
all cosy with your mother, holding her hands.
Do not do anything to upset them.
I swore to Father that I would never do anything foolish again,
so you cannot be the one to ruin it.
Whatever.
Lately, I do not know what my place is in this house.
I mean, it is not like the fixed stone...
is pushing out the one that rolled in. Seriously...
Wrong, wrong, wrong again.
The stone that rolls in pushes out the fixed stone.
Eun Su Jung. Crystal.
Please, let's just compose ourselves.
I am hanging up. Come in.
Oh my word.
I mean, what exactly does he want me to be discreet about?
Other than blabbing about the DNA test,
what else have I done wrong? Unbelievable.
Darn it.
Well, you see, for some time now,
I have caused you some unreasonable trouble,
and I want to offer my sincere apologies.
I am sorry.
You will accept my apology, will you not?
I would have to know what specifically...
you are apologising for...
For this and that. All sorts of things.
You see, now that things have come to this,
I want to accept you, Secretary Jo, as my brother-in-law...
and get along with you from now on.
You know, without being difficult, but reasonably and properly.
It is good for us to get along, but...
What is it you really want to say?
Well, about the proposal my father made last time...
The matter of being added to the family registry.
Have you reached a decision?
No, not yet.
Not yet? What is taking so long to decide?
It is a simple yes or no question.
Traditionally,
a family registry is for blood relatives.
No matter what anyone says, only Father's blood relatives...
are qualified to be on that registry, don't you think?
That is a decision for my wife to make,
so I do not believe it is my place to answer.
Seriously? I cannot understand it. The great Jo Sung Jun...
cannot even make one simple decision.
Are you henpecked, Secretary Jo? Like me?
There is something I am curious about.
Was there some special reason...
why you adopted Team Leader Ko?
What did you say?
You seem to value bloodlines more than anyone,
and there is General Director Ko. So why...
did you end up adopting Team Leader Ko?
I suddenly became curious.
Well...
Well, that is because I am a devoted son.
If my father told me to die,
I am the kind of person who would pretend to die.
I guess you did not know.
Is that all?
Well... What else would there be?
Unbelievable.
What are you doing? You can go now.
Yes, sir.
(Gangsu Construction)
- Well then. - Yes.
What is with that guy? I tried to get along with him...
and even extended an olive branch, but now he is acting up again.
Does he know something?
He was arrested and taken into custody?
Where exactly was Jung Dong Pal arrested?
In front of CS convenience store?
Yes, I understand.
No, I was just curious.
Yes.
Oh, General Director Ko, where are you now?
You are? I'll head over. Okay.
Can you give me more details?
Things were so chaotic that day.
So you're saying Seung Ri called the police...
and was then taken hostage?
- In front of CS convenience store. - Yes.
But why do you ask?
I thought something seemed strange that day too.
By any chance,
is there some kind of connection between that man and Seung Ri?
No, that's impossible.
I didn't think much of it at the time,
but it seems like what Seung Ri did was far too dangerous.
That bastard didn't threaten my daughter...
with a dangerous weapon, did he?
I'm not entirely sure,
but the police and I burst in right as she was taken hostage,
so she was freed right away.
Chief Seo.
- Are you all right? - Yes, of course I am.
Thank you. If it weren't for you, General Director Ko...
(General Director Ko Min Ho)
Chief Seo, too? Why?
I think there's something more to this.
Dad.
- Oh. - What are you doing here?
Well...
- Want dinner with me tonight? - Eat out?
Yes, that sounds great.
I'll wait for you in the lobby after work.
Okay, see you later.
What brings you here without calling?
Well,
being at home just stresses me out. Who else do I have?
You're my one and only best friend.
Best friend? Please.
I'm only your best friend when you need something.
Have a seat.
Kang Yeon Ja is at my house right now.
That mother and daughter are so incredibly close,
it's honestly sickening.
I can't even stand to look at them.
Why would you find that sickening?
They're a mother and daughter who just reunited after 50 years.
Of course they're going to be emotional.
Be honest with me.
Who is it? Me or Kang Yeon Ja?
Excuse me? What kind of question is that?
Lately, you've been icing me out and taking Kang Yeon Ja's side.
We even have a 25-year friendship.
I am not on Kang Yeon Ja's side.
That's ridiculous.
Actually, the other day,
I had a huge fight with Kang Yeon Ja.
What? Really? Why?
You see,
I can let other things slide, but when it comes to my child...
She said our Seung Woo looks like a gigolo,
- Oh my. - and then she started...
questioning his upbringing and hit him on the back.
How could I just stand by and watch?
I tell you,
if it wasn't Kang Yeon Ja, that day I would have...
Even if she is the Madam's daughter, that's too much.
My goodness. That girl is so strange.
What's wrong with Seung Woo? He's kind, handsome, and cute.
He has good manners too.
But why did she hit Seung Woo?
Her youngest daughter is working on a project with Seung Woo,
and she got drenched with water.
So she misunderstood when she saw her...
wearing his clothes.
Oh my gosh. That woman is ridiculous, right?
How did you think of coming to a place like this?
Just because. We're together at work and at home,
so I felt like we haven't had a proper date.
What exactly is a proper date?
For me, every single moment with you has been special, Eun Ae.
At first, I thought you had a real talent for saying hurtful things.
Right, what did you say to me?
You asked if I was...
getting tutored to be unlikeable, didn't you?
Did you know?
That among all those stars we see up there,
many of them have already disappeared.
Of course, I know that.
It takes light several light-years to reach Earth.
Even stars that have already disappeared,
as long as we're looking at them like this,
they still exist in a way, right?
It's the same for your father, Team Leader Ko.
What I mean is,
your father, like those stars,
is watching over you from somewhere.
You sound just like my father.
Pardon?
My mother passed away right after I was born,
and my dad always used to say that.
That my mom became a star in the sky...
and that she was watching over me.
I'd forgotten about it for a while as I grew up.
I feel like I said the wrong thing.
No, you didn't.
The story I really wanted to tell...
was about my father.
I just didn't have anyone I could open up to about it.
It's not something I could talk to my grandfather about.
Then from now on, you can tell me anything.
Everything.
On my birthday,
I blew out my candles and made a wish.
I told him...
that I wished...
I could live happily with him...
until the end of the world.
But...
my father passed away that day.
So after that,
I've lived my life...
with my heart tightly closed.
But...
the me inside is telling me...
to open that door.
Aren't you scared?
It might be such a painful memory...
that you've kept it hidden away.
I'm scared.
Very.
But I'm going to try to open it.
Whatever it may be,
I won't run away from it anymore.
You may be facing the memory alone,
but don't forget that by your side,
there are people who genuinely care for and love you.
Your grandfather, your grandmother,
and me too.
I...
will always be by your side.
Without leaving you for one moment.
Always.
Can I have your hand?
Pardon? My hand?
Team Leader Ko.
I got this a long time ago,
but I've only just now worked up the courage.
From now on...
I'm going to see this through to the end with you, Jo Eun Ae.
Does that mean...
you're not planning on going back to the States?
Maybe.
Or...
I could go with you.
Will you...
come with me...
until the end of the world?
Yes, I will.
Wherever that is, I will go with you...
to the very end.
(Our Happy Days)